{
    "id": "e78fbe3782da4097b5445d43497c1e38",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………… she saw us, she rushed towards us.",
            "description": "Either could be used here with slightly different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "As soon as",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "25c4ece7a77d46d3969526d3f2e03da6"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. I had invited all of them, none of them turned up.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "947ae6414c534e58af035ef303ae77a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns a lot of money ………………………., she spends hardly anything.",
            "description": "However is not a conjunction it is a transitional adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "however",
                "although"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06da3da597ac4271bed4951402a7bab6"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. they are poor, they cannot afford to buy a home.",
            "description": "All of these words are used to give the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "As",
                "Since",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "588b869f6b8a489999816105d76f92b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The postman came ………………………. I was mowing the lawn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "when"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97c3aaa2bdd94100b76930648e3638bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. she put in her best efforts, she could not succeed.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas even if refers to future.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "97fc96884b63443aaea3fa5e99897f9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. I had warned him, he didn’t listen to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd9e4cc17c714d238003acea21e0b07e"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. you work hard enough, you will succeed.",
            "description": "Either could be used here with different meanings if expresses a condition as gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1ddee963624a4527995149e913348dab"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. she has a university degree, she is unemployed.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "407200c96a5543c896ece63634896263"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was upset ……………………………. she had failed the test.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "though",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aec6d8170fbc417aa404afeb0f565080"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hardly had I reached the station ……………………….. the train left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e4b51e5e7c2d46e7add885b4ccf3eff2"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. she was hungry, she refused to eat anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bbd99666d6354f9badc3ef3790e903ac"
        }
    ]
}